

About Me

I am an honest, self-motivated girl with a positive attitude toward my career and my life. I hope to contribute to a peaceful society by sharing information, talents, and experiences with others while also strengthening human qualities.

- +94 70 592 34 54 / 078 49 06 882
- pananesenarathna@gmail.com
- - 60/5 B, Sucharitha MW, Siddhamulla
- Galkandarawa, Harankahawa, Haldummulla
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ma dhushani-senarathna-803bb0214

https://madhushanisenarathne.github.io/myportfolio

EXPERTISE

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Digital Marketing
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

EXPERIENCE

SENARATHNA

Social Media Coordinator

Senaro Motor Company August 2024 - Present

Web Master & Marketing Officer

Vista Campus & Foreign Education Consultants January 2024 - July 2024

Project Assistant

Lanka Jathika Sarvodaya Shramadana Sangamaya (Inc.) June 2023 - January 2024

Internship - Software Developer

SLT Digital Lab

June 2022 - December 2022

Trainee - Computer Operator

University of Sabaragamuwa 2018 - 2019

EDUCATION

BSc (hons) Information Technology - 2019 - 2023

University Of Sri Jayewardenepura | Second Class Lower GPA - 3.27

Certificate Course in Introduction to Entrepreneurship

University Of Sri Jayewardenepura

JavaScript Basics - 2021

An Online Course Through Coursera

Introduction to Cyber Security - 2021

Vocational Training Authority

Advanced Certificate in Human Resources Management - 2021

Institute of SLTC

Certificate Course in Marketing & Business Management -

Institute of SLTC

ICT (NVQ Level 4) 2019

Vocational Training Authority

G.C.E. Advanced Level - 2017 A-2 | B-1

G.C.E. Ordinary Level - 2014 A-1 | B-5 | C-1 | S-2

SKILLS

Technical Skills

- o PHP
- o HTML
- MERN
- SQL
- JavaScript

Soft Skills

- Problem Solving
- Positivity
- Critical Thinking
- o Team Work
- Flexibility

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name

Panane Ralalage Duleeka Madhushani Senarathna

Birthday

08/10/1998

Attended School

B/ Ananda National Collage -Walhaputenna

NIC Number

987822066V

Gender

Female

PROJECT

Final Year Research - 2022

Topic - Prevalence and predictive factors of perceived stress among university students using machine learning algorithms

- I published my research abstract at the Vidyodaya undergraduate research day held on February 22, 2023
- Research Implementation https://github.com/MadhuSenarathna123/final-year-research-implementation
- Trained Model

https://github.com/MadhuSenarathna123/train-stress-machine-learning-model

Mobile Application for Furniture - 2020

https://github.com/MadhuSenarathna123/Shopping_App

Inventory Management System - 2020

ttps://github.com/TharangaPremathilaka/Group6_InventoryManagementSystem

Web Application for Travel - 2021

https://github.com/MadhuSenarathna123/Shopping_App

REFERENCES

Mr. J.M.M. Nizwi

Project Director Dhamsak Mandiraya, 98, Sarvodaya Headquarters, Rawatawatta Road, Moratuwa.

Contact: 0766164546

niswi@sarvodaya.org

Mrs. Pasangi Perera

Lecturer in IT Department of ICT,

Faculty of Humanities and Social Sciences, University of Sri Jayewardenepura

Sri Lanka.

Contact: 071 738 0289

pasangiperera@sjp.ac.lk